But take your shoulders right back.
You start off by opening the sternum, the center part of your chest, promoting positive feelings in the body.
So shoulders go right back.
The arms just hang down relaxed so they can touch your thighs.
Let your chin go up and as the chin goes up toward the ceiling the thyroid is exposed.
Now here where the chest opens is a four chakra and the throat is a fifth chakra.
Take a deep breath in through your nose.
On the exhale, keeping your shoulders back, let the chin come in towards you chest.
Massaging the thyroid, inhale and lift right up tall.
Exhale, bring your chin right in towards your chest, inhale lift up tall and exhale bring your chin towards you chest.